All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, sets sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm gonna be the king of the pirates!
As Luffy and his crew push onto the New World, they make a stop on Fishman Island, where they are pulled into a civil war years in the making.
After meeting with Jinbei, they learn the history of the island and the events that led to their battle with the new Fishman Pirates.
They also learn of Queen Otohime, who despite opposition, fought tirelessly for understanding between humans and fishmen.
If I join Aladdin and the other crew members who do not wish to be pirates, no longer have to be.
They can live in this country without fear of retribution.
It's a way for me to take care of my men.
In case you forgot, Tiger is dead.
I'd love to stay and chat, but we're headed out too.
The Sun Pirates split into three groups, with Arlong, Macro, and myself as captains.
And ever since then, we have continued going our separate ways.
Shaking Fishman Island, a celestial dragon drifts in!
I can't believe we're home!
It's amazing, all right. Never thought I'd live to see this day.
You think back to how much we suffered at the hands of the Celestial Dragons, and it's no surprise we'd given up on ever seeing Fishman Island again.
And if it wasn't for Baz Tai, we'd all still be slaves on Marie Joie, and the nobles would still want to control us.
Being a pirate all these years, well, it was the only way to live.
But here we are, going home to be with our families, and we don't even have to hide.
It's happened! We're finally free!
Hey, Captain. Scratch that. I mean, Brother Jinbei. I'll never forget what you've done for all of us.
Don't get so dramatic on me.
Course not, but we still want you to know that we understand.
The only way pirates like us could truly be free is with the amnesty of the government.
Yeah, and that's why you joined the Warlords, isn't it?
We know that you did it for us, and not because you wanted to.
Alright, that's enough already. If you want to get sentimental, then save it for your families.
Look, they're anxious enough to see you as it is.
Oh, honey. That's Dad?
My love.
Don't worry. Go on.
Dad!
You're home!
Aladdin, after all those years you toiled as a slave, how does it feel to be a free fishman?
Jinbei, as you say, we are free. No longer hunted by the Celestial Dragons, at least.
And at long last, we can return to our families without fear.
But just like the mark of the Celestial Dragons, the agony that we suffered as slaves is seared into our minds.
And though we may walk this world as we please, our hatred towards humans, it will always bind our souls.
To be clear, I understand every word of what Brother Tai tried to impart.
But still...
This makes me sick.
How could Jinbei join up with humans? He's just a tool for the world government.
After everything that happened with them, too. Did he already forget who killed Fisher Tiger?
Hate to say it, but I've lost all respect for him.
I knew quite well what was waiting for me. The Islanders couldn't understand. And they reviled the fact that I joined the Warlords.
I can't imagine a more fortuitous situation. We now have a relationship with the world government thanks to Jinbei.
This is our chance. We can establish friendly relations with humans now. And I will work hard to make sure that we do.
Of course. But while I recognize why Jinbei did it, it troubles me to see him take on such a terrible burden.
If he receives an order from the world government, he'll have no choice but to fight for their cause, regardless of the circumstance.
And no matter how much he might disagree, he will be asked to stand in harm's way and his blood will be spilled.
Yes. He's making a great sacrifice. And I won't let it go to waste. I promise that I'll do my very best.
As long as you also promise me that you won't push yourself too hard, I would loathe to see you suffer another debilitating hangover.
Despite this promising turn of events, something unexpected occurred that would forever alter the path of Queen Otohime's life.
An uninvited visitor arrived on the island.
Ryugu Kingdom, come in! This is the Border Patrol! A large, badly damaged ship is seeking emergency entry into the country!
Well, what are you waiting for? Just do your job and let them in!
It's a little complicated, sir!
It belongs to... a... a Celestial Dragon!
It what?! King Neptune!
Wait, are you sure?
Grant them entry! Send a rescue team right away!
I'll go welcome them myself.
Krino Nohime!
What in the world is a Celestial Dragon doing on the seafloor?
I can't believe this is happening! Must have been attacked by a Sea King or something.
Here's what I don't get. They hate us fishmen, right? So what were they doing sailing through such deep water?
Let's help, you idiots!
My whole worthless crew just had to go and die!
Bring me a mask, you vulgar fishes!
I can't tolerate your fishman stench!
I demand that you bring me a mask!
I need you to save my life! Filthy fools!
This creep's got zero respect for us.
He thinks we're gonna help him talking to us like that?
Doctor, now!
I need help!
Are the medics here?
Well, yeah, they're here, but they're not sure if they want to help that thing.
Put him out of his misery.
He doesn't deserve to live. He's pure scum.
The Seven Warlords are a joke!
I wouldn't sell my soul to take a job working for the world government even if the bastards beg me!
Hell no! You've got way too much integrity, Captain Deakin!
Everyone talks about Jinbei like he's invincible, but he's no match for me as a pirate!
And that much is true, I suspect!
Ba-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
Huh?
Sounds like something's going on at the harbor.
Hey!
It's a celestial dragon.
Oh, man.
Looks like a world noble's causing this.
Well, that's interesting.
I guess his ship got wrecked and now he's flipping his lid or something.
Ba-ho-ho-ho! Come on, let's go check it out!
This is guaranteed to be good for a few laughs.
This is not how events were supposed to unfold.
The Fishman slaves have been allowed to return to their island!
How can this be? Daddy dear!
It's bureaucracy, my son.
The Fishman pirate Jinbei joined the Seven Warlords, and he brokered a deal.
But I don't understand!
Jinbei was the captain of the Sun Pirates.
The lowly thugs who've been hiding the slaves.
We negotiated to have their evasion charges dropped,
and obtained amnesty for the slaves to return home, you see.
But if that's the case, then they aren't just any slaves.
Some of them are probably my slaves, right, Daddy dear?
Oh, I'm certain of it, my son.
It turns my stomach to think they're living a free and easy existence after disrespecting us.
Fine then! I'll just have to hunt them down and reclaim them, won't I?
It's only right considering how much money I spent on collecting those slaves in the first place.
Zzzzzzzzzzzzzz.
Hmm, it's not fair. This should be easy.
Why didn't anyone tell me the sea floor was so unhospitable?
Hey! What do you guys think you're doing?
What do you guys think you're doing?
What?
Long time no see, Hamio's guard.
How dare you address me without my title!
Oh! You're all my slaves!
My personal property!
You must return with me at once!
Do you hear? I didn't permit you to run free!
Wait! Don't do it, you guys! He's a celestial dragon!
It'll void the amnesty if you kill him!
Put that gun down! Know your place!
You belong to me and you will do as I say!
I'm your master! Your master!
Up on the surface, all you have to do is cry and the admirals will come running to you at the drop of a hat.
You realize that's the only reason people are scared of you nobles.
But you're at the bottom of the sea floor right now.
As long as the islanders stay quiet, and trust me, they will.
Whatever happens to you, they'll think it was an accident.
Hey, he's got a point there.
I'll keep my mouth shut!
Me too! Mums the one!
Just look at that creep! He's barely even alive!
Might as well get it over with right now!
No! Make it real slow!
He should suffer the same way that you guys did!
Kill him! Make him suffer!
Don't give him any mercy!
What? But why?
I thought everyone respected me.
I can't forgive you.
Not after what you did! Not until my dying day!
No! Don't do it!
Shoot him!
Earn this life!
Don't do it!
You're just stupid fiend!
Kill him!
Oh no, they shot the queen!
Queen Otohime, I...
Everyone, drop your guns at once.
Look around, children are watching.
Aladdin, I heard about the Celestial Dragon. Where is he now?
Not sure, I just got here myself.
Boss Jinbei!
Have you seen our mother? She rushed out of the palace!
To come down here?
Hey brother, these Celestial Dragons, who are they?
They're not like us, they're humans.
Humans?
Not all humans in the world are bad, but these are not to be trusted.
I heard some gunshots right when I got here. Let's go!
Queen Otohime...
It only grazed me.
Why are you protecting him?
You have no idea what kind of pain that man inflicted on us!
The hell he put us all through!
He treated us like we were nothing more than a bunch of animals!
Almost!
I know, I can feel the anguish in your hearts. I do not question that.
Has mother been injured?
Oh no!
I know it's difficult, but you can't pollute the children's minds with your anger towards humans!
Your resentment, do not make it theirs!
They deserve the chance to meet humans and make up their own minds!
Please, you can't tell them!
You have to hold it in!
Our tragedy, and our hatred, they must die with us!
They were one and the same.
No! Watch out, Mother!
You stay still!
Your Majesty! What is this?
Mother, no!
You bastard!
This stinky fish is your queen?
While a celestial dragon bows before no one, she's just another worthless commoner!
An ignoble bottom feeder!
How dare you!
Can't someone help her?
Now, you fools!
You'll do as I say!
Bring me a mask!
And a doctor!
Because if you don't...
Mama!
What the...
The Sea King!
No!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Ah!
What the hell?
It just happened.
That was no coincidence.
Shirohoshi, are you the one who did this?
Wow, Captain, you're really freaking out.
A legend my family spoke of for all those years.
A mermaid gifted with mysterious powers.
An almost supernatural ability that allows her
to summon and control the Sea Kings.
I scoured the sea floor searching for the truth.
Searching for traces of this fabled mermaid.
My family was right!
Their dream was true!
I found her!
Wait, you think Shirohoshi's the legendary mermaid?
I knew you'd find her, Captain.
Shush!
No one else can find out about this.
It's a secret legend so old that everyone has forgotten
about it except for my family.
So I suspect.
Can you imagine?
If I could get the Sea Kings to do my bidding,
not a person alive could stop me.
I could do anything and take anything I wanted.
Bah!
So, what's the next step in the plan?
Are we gonna kidnap Princess Shirohoshi or what?
Of course not!
I simply have to make her my wife!
You do realize she's still only a child, don't you?
Yeah...
That's the problem.
Aladdin.
I'll treat him if you wish, my queen.
It's the right thing to do.
I'll take care of your wound next.
A few weeks later,
once the Celestial Dragon's health was stable enough
for him to travel home,
he prepared to disembark for his voyage.
But Queen Otohime did something rather unexpected
before he could leave.
You will pay for this, you damn fish!
You insulted and humiliated me
despite the fact that I'm a respected world noble!
Your actions were unforgivable
and you will come to regret them!
So we just saved his life
and then he turns around and threatens us?
He's got some nerve speaking to us that way.
We provided him with a ship and a crew to go home.
What the hell else does he expect from us?
We shouldn't even be letting him leave anyway.
He's a danger to the whole island.
Wait a minute!
Huh?
It's evident to me that you have more to say.
So I'll travel to the world above with you to hear you out.
She can't!
It's too dangerous!
Please don't go!
Mother, no!
You must reconsider!
I cannot allow you to face such danger
if you truly wish to negotiate with the nobles.
Allow me to go in your place!
I know you'd be safe.
You're the king and a great knight,
so the humans couldn't harm you even if they wanted to.
That's precisely why I should-
You can't!
There's no point in sending a warrior like you.
Hmm?
This is a matter of appearance.
Our nation needs to see that even someone who is as powerless as I
can travel amongst the humans and then safely return home.
That's the point.
Without fear,
and with a heart that's full of trust,
I'll go myself.
That's the only way that this can be done.
Hmm...
Be careful, Mother!
Don't go, Mother!
Reynaldo Hime!
I can't get it.
Where is she going?
My queen...
Trust in me.
Have faith in the women you married.
And the humans.
You're just the queen of a fish tank!
You arrogant trash!
Goodbye, Mother!
I will miss you!
It's troubling.
Believe me, I know how you feel, but no one can stop her.
All we can do is have faith and hope for the best.
You have to see!
Please be careful up there!
Come home safe!
I love you, Mother!
Otohime returns from the world above
with a ray of hope for Fishman Island.
Her once impossible dream now becomes the dream of her people
as one Islander after another pledges support to her cause.
But just when the path to the future seems to have opened,
a shot echoes through the plaza,
changing the course of history forever.
On the next, One Piece!
A sudden tragedy!
A gunshot shuts down the future!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
The pirates!